# Luong Minh Nhat

Software Engineer Intern



#### **Contact**



(+84) 378 - 160 - 061



luongminhnhat1604@gmail.com



Tan Phu district, Ho Chi Minh city



github.com/MinhNhatLuong

# **Hard Skills**

Programming languages: C,
 C++, Java, Javascript

• Web developer: HTML5, CSS3

• Back-end developer: MySQL

## Soft skills

- Task management
- · Curiosity and lifelong learning
- · Analytical and creative thinking
- Languages: English (Fluent),
  Japanese (Beginner), Vietnamese
  (native).

#### Introduction

I am a person with a strong passion for full-stack development. I have a keen interest in both front-end and back-end technologies and have gained hands-on experience through projects and coursework.

My goal is to become a full-stack engineer within the next three years. I would love to work with tasks such as Front-end, Back-end Developer or database building.

#### **Education**

Bachelor of Software Engineer
 FPT University - HCMC Campus

2023 - Present

### **Certificates**

- Web Design: Coding Specicialization (2024)
  Coursera University of Michigan
- C++ Programming (2023)
  F8 Fullstack
- C Programming For Beginners Master the C Language (2024)
   Udemy - Tim Buchalka

# **Professional Experience**

Web developer (UI Designer)

Skillcetera club

Nov 2023 - Mar 2024

Developing a website for selling merchandises for the Skillcetera club. I was assigned to design the interface and features for the "About Us" sections, and I also observed the work of other members to gain experience. The project involved a team of five members and was a success. Link: s-store.skillcetera.com.

#### **Extracurricular Activities**

TEDxFPTUniversity Logistic Vice Leader

Skillcetera club

Feb 2024 - Jun 2024

Arranging gifts for attendees and managing bills.

TEDxFPTUniversity Event Management Member

Skillcetera club

Febr 2024 - May 2024

Administrating outside the hall (event experience area, check-in, booth,...); Build and setup concept.

TEDxFPTUniversity Sales Member

Skillcetera club

Feb 2024 - May 2024

Planning and selling TED merchandise; supporting the customers (calling to confirm, reminders, etc.), handling on-stage tasks.